const flashcards = [
  {
    id: 1,
    category: "",
    question: "q1",
    answer:
      "q1use state is a react hook that allows us to render pages dynamically. ",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    category: "Js",
    question: "q2",
    answer:
      "q2use state is a react hook that allows us to render pages dynamically. ",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    category: "CSS",
    question: "q3",
    answer:
      "q3use state is a react hook that allows us to render pages dynamically. ",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    category: "General",
    question: "q4",
    answer:
      "q4use state is a react hook that allows us to render pages dynamically. ",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    category: "react",
    question: "q5",
    answer:
      "q5use state is a react hook that allows us to render pages dynamically. ",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    category: "React",
    question: "q6",
    answer:
      "q6use state is a react hook that allows us to render pages dynamically. ",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    category: "Html",
    question: "q7",
    answer:
      "q7use state is a react hook that allows us to render pages dynamically. ",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    category: "css",
    question: "What is block element?",
    answer:
      "block element is an html element which takes the whole width of its parent by default",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    category: "css",
    question: "What is block element?",
    answer:
      "block element is an html element which takes the whole width of its parent by default",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    category: "css",
    question: "What is block element?",
    answer:
      "block element is an html element which takes the whole width of its parent by default",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    category: "css",
    question: "What is block element?",
    answer:
      "block element is an html element which takes the whole width of its parent by default",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    category: "css",
    question: "What is block element?",
    answer:
      "block element is an html element which takes the whole width of its parent by default",
  },
];

export { flashcards };
